We had some calls earlier today
what paths could exist.
Nothing came to fruition obvious
uh sort of transpired in real time that
would have been worth even flagging.
>> These last seven eight picks looked like
teams were really looking to move down.
Is that what you expected?
>> Yeah, it felt like uh there could be a
little bit more action towards the front
half of the first than what we
ultimately ended up seeing. really
anticipated a heavy O run there in the
teens uh and throughout the early
portion uh of the 20s and then would
have anticipated that there was going to
be quite a bit of movement there towards
the back half of the first but nothing
that was going to be a substantial jump
back as much as it was those small
incremental moves into the early portion
of the second.
>> How do you feel like the board now
stacks up, you know, now that you've
seen the first 32 that are off the
board? Yeah, I think it reflects what we
were projecting and uh at this stage
we're able to take the night, circle
back tomorrow and continue our thoughts
around uh what comes here once we get up
onto the clock at 56.
>> When you don't have a pick in the first
round, how do you spend that? Are you
just still making phone calls, looking
around or are you just kind of watching
and monitoring your board?
>> Yeah, I think you're analyzing a few
different things while at the same time
enjoying how things unfold. Uh you know,
I don't know that uh there's a ton of
action that you can point to in
particular with tonight. Um, uh, like I
said before, a few different calls that
unfolded throughout the course of the
day, but really just setting any sort of
conversations that could come if the
opportunity made sense for both parties.
And, uh, tonight that wasn't the case.
>> Is it a busy day of phone calls
tomorrow?
>> I'm sorry, John.
>> Is it a busy day of phone calls tomorrow
or or is that already sort of done?
Yeah, I think most of those things are
primed ahead of time and you can do a
lot of it while teams are on the clock
or just ahead of that time.
>> Is there anything that surprised you in
this first round since it go high or
anything like that?
>> I think everybody was worthy of uh the
slots that they ended up going in and
congrats to all those guys and uh you
know looking forward to what tomorrow
brings.
>> You said uh a couple weeks ago that
defensive end was probably the strongest
group. Is there still a lot of value
there after the first run?
>> Yeah, I actually think so. I think
really all the position groups that uh
we felt like had the strength showed
itself in the in the first round and uh
there are still some spots where we feel
like the depth is healthy and others
where it has been depleted, right? And I
think that's not unlike any any other
draft, but uh certainly look forward to
navigating those waters.
>> James, you guys have um seem to embrace
being bold in the entertainment business
part of it. Is there a level of almost
disappointment when you kind of can't
make something happen? And I guess
what's the balance between that and the
discipline of not pushing it?
>> Yeah, I know we'll be strategically bold
is the important aspect to that. And uh
as it relates to how we've operated over
the course of this off season, uh
there's been a ton of intent and a ton
of discipline tied to it. And I think
the idea of a volume play is an
important thing for us to acknowledge
knowing that, you know, while uh you
date back to my time in Los Angeles,
there were quite a few drafts. we were
picking with as many as 11, 12, 13, 14
picks, and that gives you a lot more uh
chances to hit, a lot more chances to
miss. Um, but we'll take take the
chances at this stage knowing that uh we
feel good about our process. We feel
good about the collective efforts that
have brought forth the guys that we feel
really good about uh entering into our
environment and knowing that they're
rooted uh in the stuff that's only going
to point to them thriving in it. Have
you scout or evaluate or approach the
later round guys in the draft any
differently now that in the NIL era
knowing some of these guys are going to
be taking pay cuts?
>> That's interesting. I don't know that
it's rooted in financial uh thoughts as
much as it is uh you talk about age uh
quite a bit and whether or not uh tread
on the tires is something of note. Um,
so I think things like that tend to be
uh a bit more of those topics that
surface to the top. I think most of the
times the guys have a little bit more uh
financial awareness and that can be a
really helpful tool. You know, the fact
that they're not just being dumped a
good chunk of cash for the first time uh
when they enter the NFL. Uh they now
have some version of experience
navigating that. And so that can be a
really helpful piece for sure.
>> Training for bouquet last week. What do
you like about him when he kind of adds
that room and have that kind of play
out?
>> Yeah, I think the idea that he can offer
a a skill set that only enhances our
capacity to pressure the QB uh jumps out
in a real way. Um, in the same breath, I
know he offers a lot of flex flexibility
and versatility that uh we can move him
inside and out uh depending on if it's
base and sub. and uh you know excited
about the idea of of getting some fresh
legs and and really knowing that from
his vantage point. Uh he's in a spot
where he's looking forward to you know
restarting rebuilding and uh you know
when he first stopped by over the
weekend it was kind of cool. We were
poking our heads out at the new stadium
and the build. He's like you know what
this is actually a good reflection of
where I'm at in my career and look
forward to building the same way that
that stadium is across the uh across the
parking lot. So, it was a cool little
moment for him to kind of share his
perspective there and at the same time
knowing that that's a lot of the reason
why we prioritized him and why we wanted
to bring him.
>> James, couple of GMs said during their
pre-draft sessions that the 2027 draft
is strong. How much of a priority is it
this weekend to maybe add a couple of
those picks?
>> You know what? I I think that that is a
fair assessment based off of the early
showings. At the same time, uh, over the
course of the next year, there's going
to be a lot of holes that get poked
into, uh, those folks that, um, you
know, I think aren't yet to show
themselves because it's all surface
level. Um, so only time will tell
whether or not that is in fact, uh,
true. Uh, at the same time, we're going
to entertain uh, the right value and the
right thing for the organization. When
we have the chance to explore all
options, we're certainly going to do so.
How big of a step do you feel like you
guys can take tomorrow having, you know,
four selections on a roster that's
already very good and very balanced?
>> I think there's a good chance to to
really level up. I think one of the big
things that I look back to last year is
the depth of the roster as a whole being
a a really critical piece so that when
we did experience windows in which there
were heavy heavier injuries or attrition
uh that there wasn't some version of a a
critical fall off uh at any one position
and I think that that helped helped our
cause and uh certainly I think that with
what we have lying in front of us not
only tomorrow but on day three of the
draft and even following the seventh
round in undrafted college free agency.
Uh those are sort of the fringe edges
that you can win uh in a lot of ways and
make differences in uh what is going to
be a long season. And so I think that
that's something that we're certainly
excited about focusing on.
>> James, Monday you guys picked up the
fifth year option on Anton. Was that a
pretty easy decision? and and where do
you see him at this stage of of his
career as hopefully an ascending player,
I would assume.
>> Yeah, that was a a pretty
straightforward decision. and he has
really bought into uh everything that
we're trying to do and has shown steady
improvement over the course of our time
together and really look forward to him
building off of the momentum and uh you
know really across that entire offensive
line those guys were really uh finding a
cohesive means of operating and I say
that even when there were a lot of
moving parts throughout the course of
the season that's not easy to do and so
knowing that we got nine of those guys
back uh I think That was a a really
important piece for us to continue to
show uh that this is something we care
about keep keeping tied together and and
ensuring that you know whatever momentum
we were able to capture over the course
of the last season the connective tissue
that we were able to build there because
it's such a key piece to that
performance as a whole across all five
whoever's on the field. Uh we just want
to maintain that and uh this was
certainly a sign to point exactly as to
why. James, thank you for your help
tonight.